Guide to the Polytechnic Marketing and Communications CD Image Collection RG.034
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Polytechnic Marketing and Communications CD Image Collection
1990-2015
2002-2015
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
RG.034
2 Linear Feet 4 boxes (11.5 x 6.5 x 6.5")
This collection of compact discs (CDs) contains digital images of events and people related to Polytechnic. It was transferred to the Poly Archives from the Marketing and Communications Department in 2016.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into four series, by subject: students, faculty, faculty groups, and events. Items within each series is arranged alphabetically. This arrangement follows the original order of the Marketing and Communications Department.
Scope and Contents
The collection is comprised of compact discs (CDs) containing digital images of Polytechnic students, faculty, and events from 2002-2015. Some of these photographs were taken by the NYU Photo Bureau, some were taken by contracted photographers, and for some the original photographer is unknown.
Biographical / Historical
Images in this collection relate to events and people from Polytechnic University (1985 - 2008), NYU Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn (2008 - 2014), and NYU Polytechnic School of Engineering (2014 - 2015). Polytechnic University began an affiliation with New York University in 2008, which culminated in a 2014 merger. Following the merger, Polytechnic became a school within NYU.
The image CD collection was held in the Marketing and Communications Department offices until it was transferred to the Poly Archives on July 5, 2016.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials found in collection; there is no documentation concerning the provenance of these materials.
Compact discs
- Series I: Students
  - Ahmed, Omar, 2011 (Box 1, Disk 1)
  - Aristizabol, Ximenia, 2012 (Box 1, Disk 3, Disk 2)
  - Badah, Sahar, 2012 (Box 1, Disk 5, Disk 4)
  - Brown, Sukari, 2012 (Box 1, Disk 6)
  - Christopher, Robert G., undated (Box 1, Disk 7)
  - Dalcocchio, John, 2006 (Box 1, Disk 8)
  - Dingreville, Remi, 2010 (Box 1, Disk 9)
  - Fisher, Gregg S., 2009 (Box 1, Disk 10)
  - Friend, Bill, undated (Box 1, Disk 11)
  - Florill, Francesco, 2011 (Box 1, Disk 12)
  - Hsuan, Jason, 2010 (Box 1, Disk 13)
  - Landolina, Joe, 2013 (Box 1, Disk 14)
  - Mainetta and Campane, 2009 (Box 1, Disk 15)
  - Mitchko, Stephanie, 2012 (Box 1, Disk 16)
  - Molineros, Wanda, 2012 (Box 1, Disk 18, Disk 17)
  - Mousani, Susan, 2011 (Box 1, Disk 19)
  - Patrick, Daniella, 2012 (Box 1, Disk 20)
  - Roberts, Dustyn, 2011 (Box 1, Disk 21)
  - Sanchez, Daphany, 2012 (Box 1, Disk 22, Disk 24, Disk 23)
  - Schmeelk, Suzanna, 2012 (Box 1, Disk 25)
  - Schubert, Thomas, undated (Box 1, Disk 26)
  - Talwar, Tipsy, 2011 (Box 1, Disk 27)
  - Tauro, Flavic, 2011 (Box 1, Disk 28)
  - Tian, Yangzi Isabel, 2012 (Box 1, Disk 30, Disk 29, Disk 31)
  - Witek, Lukasz, 2010 (Box 1, Disk 32)
  - Poly Students Headshots, 2013 (Box 1, Disk 33, Disk 34)
  - Poly Students Headshots, 2009 (Box 1, Disk 35)
  - Poly Students, 2008 (Box 1, Disk 36)
  - Poly Students, 1990 (Box 1, Disk 37)
  - Summer Interns, 2014 (Box 1, Disk 38)
- Series II: Faculty
  - Abaide, Nicole, 2011 (Box 1, Disk 39, Disk 40)
  - Arnold, Stephen, 2009 (Box 1, Disk 41)
  - Becker, Kurt; Joyojeet Pal; Erich Kunhardt, 2010 (Box 1, Disk 42)
  - Camarda, Charles, 2008 (Box 1, Disk 43, Disk 44)
  - Camarda, Charles and Juran, 2008 (Box 1, Disk 45)
  - Cappos, Justin, 2012 (Box 1, Disk 47, Disk 46, Disk 49, Disk 48)
  - Cappos, Justin, 2014 (Box 1, Disk 50)
  - Campisi, Matt, 2013 (Box 1, Disk 52, Disk 51)
  - Chao, 2008 (Box 1, Disk 53)
  - Chao- Deep Packet Inspection, undated (Box 1, Disk 54)
  - Dubois, Robert, 2012 (Box 1, Disk 56, Disk 55)
  - Dubois, Robert; Daphany Sanchez; Isabel Tian-- Michelle's picks (Box 1, Disk 57)
  - Erkip, Elza, 2010 (Box 1, Disk 58)
  - Farrington, Anita, undated (Box 1, Disk 59)
  - Garetz, Bruce, 2012 (Box 1, Disk 60, Disk 61)
  - Ghendeham, Masaud, 2012 (Box 1, Disk 62)
  - Gross, Richard and Olga Krestyanivova, 2012 (Box 1, Disk 63)
  - Gross, Richard; Jackson; Levicky, 2008 (Box 1, Disk 64)
  - Gross, Live Interview, undated (Box 1, Disk 65)
  - Gupta, Auto Show, 2011 (Box 1, Disk 66)
  - Gupta/Coelho, undated (Box 1, Disk 67)
  - Hultin, Jerry, 2010 (Box 1, Disk 68)
  - Igel, Irena, 2011 (Box 1, Disk 69)
  - Isbister, Ketherine, 2011 (Box 1, Disk 70)
  - Iskander, Magued, 2008 (Box 1, Disk 71)
  - Jackson, Myles, 2007 (Box 1, Disk 72)
  - Kahneman, Daniel, 2011 (Box 1, Disk 73)
  - Kapila, Vikram and Magued Iskander, 2010 (Box 1, Disk 74)
  - Kaufman, Daniel, 2010 (Box 1, Disk 75)
  - Kharrami, Farshad, 2009 (Box 1, Disk 76)
  - Kim, Joo and Mamadou Dionku, 2012 (Box 1, Disk 77, Disk 78)
  - Kriftcher, Koel, 2010 (Box 1, Disk 80, Disk 79)
  - Kuangdi, Xu, undated (Box 1, Disk 81)
  - Kumar, Uday, 2011 (Box 1, Disk 82)
  - Kunhardt, Erich, 2009 (Box 1, Disk 83)
  - Lee, 2012 (Box 2, Disk 1)
  - Leslie, Christopher, 2012 (Box 2, Disk 3, Disk 2)
  - LeVon, Kalle, 2008 (Box 2, Disk 4)
  - Mandl, Ines, 2011 (Box 2, Disk 5)
  - Masoud, undated (Box 2, Disk 6)
  - Masoud and Jin, 2011 (Box 2, Disk 7)
  - Memon, Nasir, 2010 (Box 2, Disk 8)
  - Montclare, Jin and Nikhil Gupta, 2008 (Box 2, Disk 9)
  - Mugglin, David- Laser beam, 2008 (Box 2, Disk 10)
  - Mugglin, David- T-shirts, 2008 (Box 2, Disk 11)
  - Nou, Oded, 2012 (Box 2, Disk 12)
  - Porfini, Maurizio, 2008 (Box 2, Disk 13)
  - Porfini, Maurizio, 2009 (Box 2, Disk 14)
  - Porfini, Maurizio Summer research, 2010 (Box 2, Disk 15)
  - Porfini, Maurizio and Robotic Fish, undated (Box 2, Disk 16)
  - Porfini, Maurizio, 2013 (Box 2, Disk 17, Disk 18)
  - Rappaport, Ted, 2012 (Box 2, Disk 20, Disk 19)
  - Levicky, Rasti, 2009 (Box 2, Disk 21)
  - Reiser, Arnost, 2011 (Box 2, Disk 22)
  - Rekow, Dianne, 2011 (Box 2, Disk 23)
  - Salesnick, Ivan and Jin Kim, 2008 (Box 2, Disk 24)
  - Silva, Claudio, 2012 (Box 2, Disk 25)
  - Ubell, Bob, 2012 (Box 2, Disk 26)
  - Ulman, Abraham and Joe Landolina, 2013 (Box 2, Disk 27)
  - Viventi, Johnathan, 2014 (Box 2, Disk 28)
  - Viventi, Johnathan and students, 2012 (Box 2, Disk 29)
- Series III: Faculty Groups
  - Frank, Suel, Steele, Chiang, 2013 (Box 2, Disk 31, Disk 30)
  - Ross, Freira, Silva, undated (Box 2, Disk 32)
  - Skelton, Garetz, Kim, 2010 (Box 2, Disk 33)
  - Poly Faculty Outside, 2011 (Box 2, Disk 34)
  - Headshots, undated (Box 2, Disk 35)
  - Headshots, 2013 (Box 2, Disk 35)
  - Headshots, 2014 (Box 2, Disk 37, Disk 36)
  - Poly Summer Labs, 2014 (Box 2, Disk 40, Disk 39, Disk 38)
  - Poly Scientist Group Photos, 2014 (Box 2, Disk 41)
  - Poly, 2013 (Box 2, Disk 42, Disk 43)
  - Women of Poly, 2011 (Box 2, Disk 44)
  - Women Photoshoot for Cable, 2011 (Box 2, Disk 45)
- Series IV: Events
  - Against White, Mamadou Dianko, 2012 (Box 2, Disk 46)
  - AIT (CIO) Conference, 2008 (Box 2, Disk 47)
  - Beth Altrin- Engineering and Technology Forum, 2012 (Box 2, Disk 49, Disk 48)
  - Alumni Conference and Lunch, 2010 (Box 2, Disk 50)
  - Alumni Day, 2013 (Box 2, Disk 51)
  - Alumni Photos for Cable, 2010 (Box 2, Disk 52)
  - Joanne Alzenberg Speaker, 2011 (Box 2, Disk 53)
  - MTA App Quest Awards, 2013 (Box 2, Disk 54)
  - Polytechnic Artwork, 2007 (Box 2, Disk 55)
  - Back to School Day, 2012 (Box 2, Disk 56)
  - Ben Strauss Forum, 2012 (Box 2, Disk 57)
  - BEST Center (Box 2, Disk 58)
  - Bloomberg, 2012 (Box 2, Disk 59)
  - Blue Jay Photos, undated (Box 2, Disk 60)
  - Poly Breakfast, 2009 (Box 2, Disk 61)
  - Poly Breakfast, 2007 (Box 2, Disk 62)
  - Broad Street, 2009 (Box 2, Disk 63)
  - Brooklyn Community Foundation, 2011 (Box 2, Disk 64)
  - Bugliarello Memorial, 2011 (Box 2, Disk 65)
  - Building Spaces, undated (Box 2, Disk 66)
  - Cable- Winter 2012 (Box 2, Disk 67)
  - Campus Transformation, 2014 (Box 2, Disk 68)
  - Campus Transformation, 2012 (Box 2, Disk 69)
  - CAPCO Conference, 2011 (Box 2, Disk 70)
  - Car, 2011 (Box 2, Disk 71, Disk 72)
  - Career Day, 2010 (Box 2, Disk 73)
  - CBAS Symposium, 2008 (Box 2, Disk 74)
  - Chairman Genachowski FCC, 2010 (Box 2, Disk 75)
  - Chemistry Over Coffee featuring Eli Pearce, 2014 (Box 2, Disk 76)
  - Charugundla Collection, 2013 (Box 2, Disk 77)
  - Chevalier, undated (Box 2, Disk 78)
  - Cinderella or Cyberella, 2013 (Box 2, Disk 79)
  - CITE Game Innovation Lab, 2011 (Box 2, Disk 80)
  - Cocktails- William Friend, 2013 (Box 2, Disk 81)
  - Weiner-Camarda Classroom, 2009 (Box 2, Disk 82)
  - Commencement 2008 (Box 3, Disk 1)
  - Commencement 2009 (Box 3, Disk 2)
  - Commencement 2009 (Box 3, Disk 3)
  - Commencement 2011 (Box 3, Disk 4)
  - Commencement 2011- Hultin and Miller (Box 3, Disk 5)
  - Commencement 2012 (Box 3, Disk 6, Disk 7, Disk 8)
  - Commencement 2014 (Box 3, Disk 9)
  - Convocation 2008 (Box 3, Disk 10)
  - Convocation 2009 (Box 3, Disk 11)
  - Convocation 2010 (Box 3, Disk 13, Disk 12)
  - Convocation 2011 (Box 3, Disk 14)
  - Convocation 2014 (Box 3, Disk 15)
  - Convocation, undated (Box 3, Disk 16)
  - Crickets, 2010 (Box 3, Disk 17, Disk 18)
  - CSAW 2007 (Box 3, Disk 19)
  - CSAW 2008 (Box 3, Disk 20)
  - CSAW 2009 (Box 3, Disk 23, Disk 24, Disk 21, Disk 22)
  - CSAW PM, 2010 (Box 3, Disk 26, Disk 25)
  - CSAW Team Leaders, 2010 (Box 3, Disk 29)
  - CSAW 2011 (Box 3, Disk 30, Disk 32, Disk 31)
  - CSAW 2012 (Box 3, Disk 33)
  - CSAW Cybersecurity Summer Bootcamp, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 34)
  - CSAW 2013 (Box 3, Disk 35)
  - CSAW, undated (Box 3, Disk 36)
  - Cultural Diffusion, undated (Box 3, Disk 37)
  - Poly Cyber 2012 (Box 3, Disk 38)
  - The Second Cyber Security Lecture, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 39)
  - Cyber Security Lecture, 2013 (Box 3, Disk 40)
  - Poly Cyber- Sloan Lecture, 2015 (Box 3, Disk 41)
  - NYC Design Service Jam, 2013 (Box 3, Disk 42)
  - Dibner 2nd Floor Room Shots, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 44, Disk 43)
  - Digital Media Showcase, 2013 (Box 3, Disk 45)
  - Earth Day Celebration, 2010 (Box 3, Disk 46)
  - EIA Event, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 48, Disk 47)
  - Events 2013 (Box 3, Disk 49)
  - EWB, undated (Box 3, Disk 50)
  - Poly Exteriors, 2005 (Box 3, Disk 51)
  - FCC, 2010 (Box 3, Disk 52)
  - FDNY, undated (Box 3, Disk 53)
  - Female Students, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 54)
  - Flower Lights, undated (Box 3, Disk 55)
  - Four Guys, 2008 (Box 3, Disk 56)
  - Fraida Fund, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 57)
  - Cliff Friedman- Poly Lecture, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 58, Disk 59)
  - G4 Tower, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 60)
  - NYU-Poly Gala, 2015 (Box 3, Disk 62, Disk 61)
  - Girls High School, 2011 (Box 3, Disk 63)
  - Global Exchange Idea Luncheon, 2013 (Box 3, Disk 64)
  - Golden Jubilee- Class of 1959, 2009 (Box 3, Disk 65)
  - Gowanus Canal, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 66, Disk 67)
  - Polytechnic University Graduation, 2007 (Box 3, Disk 68)
  - Groups for Identifying, 2010 (Box 3, Disk 69)
  - Hackathon, 2013 (Box 3, Disk 71, Disk 70)
  - Headshots, 2011 (Box 3, Disk 72)
  - Honorary Degree, 2007 (Box 3, Disk 73)
  - iCorps Opening, 2013 (Box 3, Disk 75, Disk 74)
  - Identity System Workshop, 2007 (Box 3, Disk 76)
  - Igert-Crissp Kickoff Workshop, 2011 (Box 3, Disk 77)
  - Incubator Anniversary, 2010 (Box 3, Disk 78)
  - Incubator Anniversary, 2013 (Box 3, Disk 79)
  - Incubator- DUMBO, 2011 (Box 3, Disk 80)
  - Incubator- DUMBO, 2013 (Box 3, Disk 81, Disk 82)
  - Incubator- Mayor, undated (Box 3, Disk 83)
  - Incubator- Press Conference, 2009 (Box 3, Disk 85, Disk 84)
  - Incubator- Varick St., 2012 (Box 3, Disk 86)
  - Indian Art Opening, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 87)
  - Inno/Vention Awards 2010 (Box 3, Disk 88)
  - Inno/Vention Awards 2013, 2011 (Box 3, Disk 89)
  - Inno/Vention Demo Day, 2013 (Box 3, Disk 90, Disk 91)
  - Inno/Vention Greenhouse Opening, 2013 (Box 3, Disk 92)
  - Inno/Vention Kickoff, 2013 (Box 3, Disk 93)
  - Inventing Awards, 2007 (Box 3, Disk 94)
  - Job Fair, 2008 (Box 3, Disk 84, Disk 83, Disk 82)
  - John DiMatteo Freshman Forum, 2010 (Box 3, Disk 85)
  - Joseph Stiglitz Lecture, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 86)
  - Lacrosse, 2008 (Box 3, Disk 87)
  - Leadership Breakfast, 2010 (Box 3, Disk 88)
  - Leadership Forum, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 89)
  - Lecture- A New Civics for Smart Cities, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 90)
  - Legeros/Ghandehari, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 91)
  - Lego Competition 2010 (Box 3, Disk 92)
  - Lego Competition and High School Robotics Lunch, 2011 (Box 3, Disk 93)
  - Lego Competition 2013 (Box 3, Disk 95, Disk 94)
  - Lego First- Polybots, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 96)
  - Levicky, Seeman, Canary, undated (Box 3, Disk 97)
  - Dawn Library and Lobby, 2007 (Box 3, Disk 98)
  - Library Cafe Opening, 2010 (Box 3, Disk 99)
  - High School Life Science Program, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 100)
  - NYU Poly Life Sciences, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 101)
  - Livable Cities of the Future, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 102)
  - Lynford Lecture 2008 (Box 3, Disk 103)
  - Lynford Lecture 2009 (Box 3, Disk 104)
  - Lynford Lecture 2011 (Box 3, Disk 105)
  - MAGNET, New Gaming Area, Town Hall, John Sexton, Board Dinner, 2013 (Box 3, Disk 106)
  - Maker Fair, 2011 (Box 3, Disk 107)
  - Poly- Math Fellowship, 2012 (Box 3, Disk 108, Disk 109)
  - Poly Media Center Event, 2008 (Box 3, Disk 110)
  - Media Event, 2010 (Box 4, Disk 1)
  - Poly Media Senator, 2008 (Box 4, Disk 3, Disk 2)
  - 500 Years of Melancholia in Mathematics, 2014 (Box 4, Disk 4)
  - NYU Poly Merger Reception, 2014 (Box 4, Disk 5)
  - Marissa Mayer- Google, 2011 (Box 4, Disk 6)
  - North America Cyberspace, 2011 (Box 4, Disk 7)
  - National Society of Black Engineers, 2012 (Box 4, Disk 8)
  - NYC Media Lab Announcement, 2010 (Box 4, Disk 9)
  - NYC Media Lab, 2011 (Box 4, Disk 10)
  - Patent Awards, 2011 (Box 4, Disk 11)
  - NYU-Poly Photo Shoot, 2011 (Box 4, Disk 12)
  - Poly Portraits, 2010 (Box 4, Disk 13)
  - Polytech #2, 2007 (Box 4, Disk 14)
  - Polytech #3, 2007 (Box 4, Disk 15)
  - Polytech #4, 2007 (Box 4, Disk 16)
  - Polytechnic Reporter, 2012 (Box 4, Disk 17)
  - Polytechnic Research Studies Exhibition, 2007 (Box 4, Disk 18)
  - Poly Signs, 2009 (Box 4, Disk 19)
  - Poly Awards, 2008 (Box 4, Disk 20)
  - Pre-Commencement Dinner, 2009 (Box 4, Disk 21)
  - Premium Technology, 2012 (Box 4, Disk 22)
  - Premium Technology Ken Leung, 2012 (Box 4, Disk 23)
  - Pres. Commendation, 2012 (Box 4, Disk 24)
  - President's Service Medal, 2006 (Box 4, Disk 25)
  - Promise Fund Dinner, 2007 (Box 4, Disk 26)
  - Promise Fund Reception, 2008 (Box 4, Disk 27)
  - Promise Fund Scholarship Reception, 2009 (Box 4, Disk 28)
  - Promise Fund Video, 2007 (Box 4, Disk 29)
  - Poly- Two Presidents, 2008 (Box 4, Disk 30)
  - Poly Thinking Posters, undated (Box 4, Disk 31)
  - Research Expo, 2013 (Box 4, Disk 32, Disk 33)
  - Ribbon Cutting, 2012 (Box 4, Disk 34)
  - Robots 2007 (Box 4, Disk 35)
  - Robots 2008 (Box 4, Disk 36)
  - Robotics 2010 (Box 4, Disk 37)
  - Robot Lab with High School Teachers, 2011 (Box 4, Disk 38)
  - Poly Robotics with iPad, 2012 (Box 4, Disk 39, Disk 40, Disk 41, Disk 42)
  - Roughead, undated (Box 4, Disk 43)
  - Science of Smart Cities, undated (Box 4, Disk 44)
  - Scientific American, 2013 (Box 4, Disk 45)
  - Security Awards, 2008 (Box 4, Disk 46)
  - SEED- Poly Grant Reception, 2009 (Box 4, Disk 47)
  - Ned Seeamn, undated (Box 4, Disk 48)
  - Service Awards 2009 (Box 4, Disk 49)
  - Service Awards 2011 (Box 4, Disk 50)
  - Service Awards 2014 (Box 4, Disk 51)
  - Social Media, undated (Box 4, Disk 52)
  - Soros Bio, 2002 (Box 4, Disk 53)
  - Sound Room, 2007 (Box 4, Disk 54)
  - Ben Strauss- Poly Forum, 2012 (Box 4, Disk 55)
  - Summer Research Headshots, 2012 (Box 4, Disk 56)
  - Summer Research Reception, 2012 (Box 4, Disk 57)
  - Swami Lecture, undated (Box 4, Disk 58)
  - Teachers Awards, 2011 (Box 4, Disk 59)
  - Toast 2009 (Box 4, Disk 60)
  - Toast 2012 (Box 4, Disk 61, Disk 62)
  - Toast 2013 (Box 4, Disk 63)
  - Poly Town Hall, 2010 (Box 4, Disk 64)
  - Poly Town Hall Ribbon Cutting, 2010 (Box 4, Disk 65)
  - Town Hall Meeting, 2011 (Box 4, Disk 66)
  - John Trani Forum, 2011 (Box 4, Disk 67)
  - Trustee Lunch, 2011 (Box 4, Disk 68)
  - Urban Future Lab, 2014 (Box 4, Disk 69)
  - Undefined, undated (Box 4, Disk 70)
  - Varick St. Incubator, 2009 (Box 4, Disk 71, Disk 72)
  - NYU-Poly Varick St. "Selects", 2010 (Box 4, Disk 73)
  - Varick St. Bloomberg, 2010 (Box 4, Disk 74)
  - Varick St., 2013 (Box 4, Disk 76, Disk 75)
  - Poly WEST, undated (Box 4, Disk 77)
  - WEST Symposium, 2011 (Box 4, Disk 78)
  - Polytech Wireless, 2012 (Box 4, Disk 79)
  - Women's Summit, 2012 (Box 4, Disk 80)
  - Women's Cyber Security Symposium, 2015 (Box 4, Disk 81, Disk 82)
  - World Science Day, 2013 (Box 4, Disk 84, Disk 83)
  - World Science Festival, 2011 (Box 4, Disk 85)
  - World Science Festival, undated (Box 4, Disk 86)